Guide to the New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records, [ca. 1960-2011]
New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records
- Series I. Administrative Files
  - General
    - Bay Area Video Coalition (BAVC) Conference, 1993, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      conservation roundtable summery and list of participants (1995, conference schedule for Playback 1996
    - Library of Congress, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      transcript of an interview with Carlisle Hart (1996), preservation materials from the Library of Congress including a survey and A Film Preservation Plan
    - New York Video Meeting Group, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Media Alliance - NEH grant applications for preservation and access (1996 and 1997); audio visual cataloging materials (1995-1996), Association of Moving Image Archivists (1996)
    - Surveys, 1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Surveys, Media Arts Breakfast Group meeting notes, Roadmap for the Information Superhighway
  - Set in Motion Artist Files
    - Richard Arlyck - Current Events, 1986, 1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      study guides, programs for other films by Ralph Arlyck, list of exhibitions and productions of Power Booth
    - (unlabelled) 85-86 Lizzie Borden Working Girls, 1987, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      press release including still photos; news clippings. NOTE: folder also includes unrelated materials from Christa Victoria's Finding Christina; Maria Beatty's Sphinxes Without Secrets: Women Performance Artists Speak Out; The Shvitz The Steambath; Joan Braderman's Joan Sees Stars; Helen Borten's A Sense of Place; Skip Battaglia's Boccioni's Bike; Ain't Nobody
    - 78-79 Kenneth Burns (Florentine Films) - Brooklyn Bridge, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
      press release
    - 78-79 Roberta Cantow - Clothesline, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      copies of news clippings, follow-up questionnaire (1981), progress report (1984), resume for Shirley Clarke and Roy Campanella II, clippings abut In Our Own Backyard a film about Love Canal
    - (unlabelled) Roberta Cantow, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, fliers for screenings, report to NYSCA (1984), Roberta Cantow resume, study guide for The Book of Laughs
    - 79-80 Howard Danelowitz - Lady Tree, c. 1980, 1991, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
      follow-up study questionnaire, information for a film Green Streets and filmmaker Maria De Luca
    - 85-86 Peter Davis - Mandella, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      lecture about the film (1986), distribution plans (1986), flier for screening What Could you do with a Nickle
    - Deborah Dickson Frances Steloff: Memoirs of a Bookseller, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      press release, fliers for screenings
    - Downtown Community TV - Healthcare: Your Money or Your Life, c. 1977, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Fliers for screening, Keiko Tsuno resume, news clippings
    - 84-85 Sara Driver - Sleepwalker, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      copies of news clippings, correspondence
    - 81-82 Kavery Dutta and Vernica Selver - With Cuban Eyes, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Film First Look, follow-up questionnaire, copies of news clippings, press release, report on the film
    - 83-84 Jose Ponce and Doug Eisenstark - Dominos and Democracy, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Fliers for screenings, proposal summary(1986-1987), copies of clippings
    - Barbara Kopple - Harlan Country, USA, 1981-1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      copies of news clippings, correspondence, grant application materials,
    - 81-82 Marjorie Keller - Sentimental Education, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Correspondence
    - 81-82 Woodie King, Jr. - Sunday, February 21, 1965: The Day Malcolm X was Killed, c. 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      press release and 1981-1985 production grant budget form
    - 87-88 Roland Legiardi-Laura - Azul, 1989, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
      news clippings, press packet
    - 82-83 Robert Longo - Empire, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      script with storyboard images, press release - including information on performers (CINDY SHERMAN)
    - 84-85 Spike Lee - She's Gotta Have It, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      news clippings, Summary of the film, resumes, portion of the script
    - 82-83 Manny Kirchheimer - Tall, Taller, Tallest, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - FY1990 Ricahrd Kilberg - Adam Clayton Powell, Jr., c. 1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      poster/study guide for the film with background material
    - 86-87 Jennie Livingston - Paris is Burning, 1986-1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Flier, copies of news clippings, correspondence
    - 81-82 Su Friedrich - Sudden Comfort, 1981-1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      follow-up questionnaire, copies of news clippings, information on later films made by Su Friedrich
    - 77-78 Susan Fanshell - Made in the Bronx, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Fliers, news clippings, correspondence
    - 81-82 Steven Fischler and Joel Sucher - Anarchism in America, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
      follow-up questionnaire
    - FY1991 Holly Fisher - Bullets for Breakfast, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      press packet for the premier at the Berlin International Film Festival
    - 81-82 Janet Forman and Tom Houghton - The Beat Generation, 1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
      press package, copy of press clippings, summery of the film and production
    - 82-83 Roman Foster and Bill Miles - Diggers, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Correspondence, press packet, copies of news clippings
    - 83-84 Hollis Frampton - R, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - 86-87 Alan Francovitch - The Houses are Full of Smoke, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      copies of news clippings
    - 83-84 Bonnie Friedman - Anzia Yezerska, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Fliers for The Flashettes and The Last to Know
    - 85-86 Grahame Weinbren and Roberta Friedman - The Erl King, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Installation notes, fliers for show
    - 77-78 Crystal Field - The Red Kimono, 1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
      follow-up questionnaire and correspondence
    - Su Friedrich - Women Make Movies, 1988, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Filmography, correspondence
    - 81-82 Ana Maria Garcia - La Operacion, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Fliers for screening, study guide for the film
    - 87-88 Amy Goldstein - Because the Dawn, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Press release for premiere, copies of news clippings, poster, black and white film stills
    - 82-83 Bette Gordon - Variety, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      review, correspondence, black and film stills, copies of news clippings, summery of Hold My Life, flier for film
    - 84-85 Sharon Greytak -, 1986-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
      copies of news clippings for Weirded Out and Blown Away, press releases for the films
    - 81-82 George Griffin - Food Stuff, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      Fliers for films by George Griffin, correspondence,
    - 79-80 Robert Gardner - Clarence and Angel, 1993-1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
      Correspondence and follow-up questionnaire
    - Jill Godmilow - Far From Poland, 1981, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
      press materials, correspondence, synopsis, budget, copy of news clippings
    - Julie Gustafson and John Reilly - Pursuit of Happiness, 1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Correspondence, resume for Julie Gustafson, copies of news clippings
    - FY1991 Todd Haynes - Poison, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      copies of news clippings - film was at the center of a government sponsored grant-funding scandal.
    - 82-83 Sally Heckel - The Female Man, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      synopsis, correspondence, script
    - FY1989 Robby Henson - Trouble Behind, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      Correspondence, flier for screening, copies of news clippings,
    - 77-78 Leo Hurwitz - Dialogue with a Woman Departed, 1982-1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
      press packet, fliers and poster for screenings, correspondence
    - 83-84 Lisa Hsia - Overseas Chinese, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      Fliers for screenings
    - FY1991 Amy Harrison - Art Guerrillas, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - (unlabelled) Barbara Margolis - Are We Winning Mommy? America and the Cold War, 1976, 1987-1988, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
      Flier and study guide for Are We Winning Mommy? America and the Cold War and synopsis of On the Line, copies of news clippings
    - 81-82 Bienvenida Matias and Marci Reaven - Through Young Peoples Eyes, 1989, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
      copies from the Cinema Guide Catalogue and a flier for The Blind Leading the Blind
    - Christa Maiwald - Van Gogh's Bedroom, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      Correspondence, film stills, resume for Yvonne Rainer
    - 86-87 Frank Moore and Jim Self - The Miller's Wife, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      press release and flier for film flier
    - 85-86 Errol Morris - New Roads, Louisiana, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      news clippings, correspondence
    - Jane Morrison - The Two Worlds of Angelita, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
      Grant report, follow-up questionnaire, poster, invitation to the premiere, press book, news clippings
    - 79-80 Charles Musser - Before the Nickelodeon, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      Flier for screening, correspondence, copies of news clippings, final grant report, poster,
    - 85-86 Sheila McLaughlin - She Must be Seeing Things, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      press release, news clipping
    - 82-83 Muffie Meyer and Ellen Hovde - Going Home, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      Correspondence (single letter)
    - 88-89 House Foundation for the Arts Book of Days, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      press packet, poster, news clipping for film by Meredith Monk
    - (unlabelled) Mira Nair - India Cabaret, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
      Flier for screening, press clipping
    - (unlabelled) Christine Noschese - Metropolitan Avenue, c. 1986-1986 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      news clippings, poster
    - 82-83 Marva Nabili - Nightsong, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      Correspondence, news clippings, concerns about the portrayal of the Asian American community, poster, synopsis
    - Nam June Paik - Allen N' Allen's Complaint, 1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
      profile in Paik in the New Yorker (1975) and Art in America (1993), artist bio, memo for National Medal of Arts
    - 74-75 Yvonne Rainer - The Man who Envied Women, 1975, 1985, 1990, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
      copies of news clippings, press releases,
    - Mark Rappaport - Chain Letters, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      single postcard
    - Martha Rosler - The Strange Case of Baby S/M, c. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      Correspondence and CV for Martha Rosler
    - Dan Reeves - Smothering Dreams, 1986, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      Correspondence, copies of news clippings, copies of film still
    - Susan and Alan Raymond - Police Tapes, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      Correspondence, synopsis, press release, film biographies for Alan and Susan Raymond, poster, fliers
    - Lucille Rhodes and Margaret Murphy (Bi-Cen) - Neel, Rukeyser, Sokolow, 1976-1980, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      Correspondence; news clippings; resumes for Margret Murphy and Lucille Rhodes; IRS investigation of grant; film summery
    - 81-82 Alfred Santana - African Religions in America, 1987, 1995, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
      press packet, news clippings
    - 82-83 Greta Schiller - Before Stonewall, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      press releases, fliers, copies of news clippings, correspondence,
    - 85-86 Greta Schiller - International Sweethearts of Rhythm, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      Fliers doe screenings, copy of news clipping
    - 83-84 Kathe Sandler - A Question of Color, 1984-1987, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      Correspondence, copies of news clippings, progress report, press packet
    - 82-83 Ricahrd Schmeichen - Out of Order, 1983-1985, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      Also known as The Times of Harvey Milk, correspondence, press releases, Academy Award nomination program, copies of news clippings
    - Frank Semmens, c. 1984 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      film calendar for A Tale of Two Serpents, flier for Mohawk Basket-making: A Cultural Profile
    - 82-83 Jackie Shearer - Don't Take Low, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 74)
      sequence outline, correspondence
    - 78-79 Stuart Sherman - Short Films, 1981,1982, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
      copies of news clippings, follow-up questionnaire
    - Peggy Stern - Stephanie, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      press packet, flier, correspondence
    - 87-88 Deborah Schaffer - Fire From the Mountain, c. 1987, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      press packet, poster, final NYSCA report for the film The Uprising of 1934
    - 81-82 Brent Owens - A Cry for Help, 1981-1988 (Box 5, Folder 78)
      Correspondence from the Black Filmmaker Foundation and NYSCA, news clippings
    - 82-83 Jan Oxenberg - Thank You and Good Night, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 79)
      synopsis, correspondence
    - 81-82 Anita Thatcher - Loose Corners, 1977-1986 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      press packet, correspondence, NEA and NEH grant applications
    - 87-88 Jonas Mekas This is My Life on Earth, 1977-1986 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      NOTE: contents not related to label. Update on Daniel J. Monahan's The Celestial Child; work in progress report for Housebreak; final report for Sorrel Hays' Sound Shadows; final report for Unknown Soldiers
    - Francesco Torres - Belchite -South Bronx: A Trans-Historical, Tans-Cultural Landscape, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - FY1991 Ela Troyano - Once Upon a Time in the Bronx, c. 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Correspondence, application for distribution
    - Rea Tajiri - History and Memory, c. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Correspondence, CV for Rea Tajiri
    - Karen Thorsen - James Baldwin, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      press packet, correspondence, news clippings
    - Claudia Weill (Bi-Cen) - Manhattan Project, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, copies of news clippings, grant application materials
    - Ira Wohl - Best Boy, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 81-82 Jeff Wisotsky - The Subway Fantasy, 1977-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      copis of news clippings, letters of support, fliers for other films
    - 78-79 Susan Wittenberg and Carol Stein - Brighton Beach, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Correspondence, copy of news clippings, program for a screening at the International Museum of Photography
    - 83-84 Calvin Wong - This Generation, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Notice of Grant, correspondence
    - John Cadigan - People Say I'm Crazy, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      press packet
    - Set in Motion Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      35mm SLIDES, invoice, and Art in America article for Shigeko Kubota's Skater; correspondence for William Garcia's One Day at a Time; Leandro Katz's Mirror on the Moon and Third World News Reel A Litany for Survival the Life and Work of Audre Lorde
    - Production Photos, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Electronic Media and Film Program: Grant Applicants and Award Winners 2002-2003
    - #1 Anne Aghion - Gacaca, Living Together Again in Rwanda?, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Correspondence, press releases, news clippings, synopsis
    - #3 Natalia Almada - All Water has a Perfect Memory, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      press packet, correspondence
    - #10 Robert Beavers - The Ground and the Hedge Theater, 1989, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Millennium Film Journal from 1989, correspondence, copy of news clipping
    - #15 Steve Bottino - The Zucchini Brothers, Live at the Clubhouse, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Correspondence, press packet
    - #16 Monika Bravo - September 10, 2001, Uno Nunca Muere La Vispera, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Correspondence, copies of news clippings, brochure for gallery show
    - #24 Jean Carlomusto and Jane Rosett - The Portrait Gallery, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Correspondence, flier, copy of a news clipping
    - #26 Seoungho Cho - Cold Pieces 2, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - #27 Jay Corcoran - Undetectable, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Flier for screening, correspondence
    - #28 Alison Cornyn and Sue Johnson The Sonic Memorial Project, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - #29 Norman Cowie - Scenes from an Endless War, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - #30 Sari Raissa Lluch Dalena - Memories of a Forgotten War, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      disbursement request form, correspondence, fliers for screening
    - #32 Ryan Deussing - Confederacy Theory, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      Correspondence, flier for screening
    - #37 Toni Dove - Sally or The Buble Burst, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      Correspondence, interview with the artist, film stills
    - #40 Alice Elliot - The Collector of Bedford Street, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - #42 Nashid Fareed Representing 11 artists - Call to Media Action (9/11), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Correspondence, flier for a screening
    - #45 Su Friedrich - The Odds of Recovery, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - #53 Julia R. Heyward - Miracles in Reverse, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Correspondence, CV for Julia Heyward
    - #24 Harriet Hirshorn and Chrintine Cynn - Pote Mak Sonje: The Raboteau Trial, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - #59 Ken Jacobs - Circling Zero-art One: We See Absence, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Correspondence, flier for screening, notes for speech at first screening
    - #77 Hans Michaud - Nine Through Twelve, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - #78 Mann Mikas - Interactive Audio Response Kit, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      Correspondence, press kit
    - #81 Ricardo J. Miranda - Vagamundo: A Migrant's Tale, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      Correspondence, description of the project
    - #91 Yvonne Rainer - After Many a Summer Dies the Swan: Hybrid, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - #95 Tome Roe - Constructive Engangement, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Correspondence, press materials
    - #99 Persheng Sadegh-Vaziri - Women Like Us, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      Correspondence, fliers for film
    - #112 Casper Stracke - No Damage, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      Correspondence, Biography of Casper Stracke
    - #117 The E-Team - The E-Team CD-Rom, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - #120 Joyce Warshow - Hand on the Pulse, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      Correspondence, distribution application, copies of news clippings,
    - #121 Katharina Weingartner - Too Soon for Sorry, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      Correspondence, press release
    - #122 Hannah Weyer - La Escuela, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - #2 Angela Alston - Reclaiming Water, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      Correspondence, distribution application press release
    - #4 Maria Antelman - The Little Emotional Controller, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - #5 David Baeumler - No Day No Night, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      Correspondence, film stills
    - #8 Michele Beck and Jorge Calvo - For to End Yet Again, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - #9 Jamyla and Pierre Bennu - Red Bone Guerillas, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - #10 Allison Berg - Witches in Exile, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 48)
      Correspondence, flier
    - #12 Alina and Jeff Bliumis - Videolog, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 49)
      Correspondence, press release, flier for screening
    - #13 Diane Bonder - Closer to Heaven, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 50)
      Correspondence, fliers, copies of news clippings, CV for Diane Bonder
    - #14 Helen Borten - Laugh Tracks, Part One and Part Two, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - #16 Torsten Zenas Burns and Darin Martin - Learning Stalls: Modular Syllabi and Organic Exchange, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      Correspondence, CVs for Torsten Zenas Burns, Darrin Martin
    - #17 Mike Camoin - Battle of Saratoga, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - #19 Paul Chan - Happiness (Finally) After 35,000 Years of Civilization, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - #19 Varick Chittendon - Masters of North Country Music Traditions, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      Correspondence, samples of promotional materials
    - #20 Seoungho Cho - Lines 1, 2, 3, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - #22 Bill Creston - Taxi, Taxi, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - #24 Menachem Daum and Oren Rudavsky - Hiding and Seeking, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - #25 Ghen Dennis - The Noise at the Other End of the Line: A Three part Series of Films, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - #26 Gearoid Dolan - Drive-By, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      Correspondence and press materials
    - # Philip Dolin - B Movie, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      Correspondence, distribution application, fliers
    - #29 Jennifer Dworkin - Love and Diane, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - #30 Alexis J. Estevez - Animus, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - #31 David Finkelstein - Radiant Emanators, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      Correspondence, press release, copies of news clippings
    - #32 Peter Friedman - Silverlake Life: Epilogue, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      Correspondence, copies of news clippings from 1993
    - #34 Pearl Gluck - Divan, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      Correspondence, copies of news clippings, synopsis, fliers
    - #35 Shalom Gorewitz - Collection: 2003, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - #36 Joan Grossman - Accidents of Memory, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - #37 Nyriam Hammani - Sisters of Algiers, Talk to Me, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - #39 Katherine Hardy - Disquiet, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - #40 Dee Henoch - Joe Chaikin's Life in the Theater, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      Fliers, correspondence
    - #42 Stephan Hillerbrand - Blue Meditation v. 04 HAL, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - #43 Shaun Irons and Lauren Petty - Dream of Automatic Release, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      press releases, fliers, correspondence
    - #45 Ken Jacobs - Star Spangled to Death, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - #46 Tyler Jacobsen - Switched P2P Application, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 75)
      Correspondence, proposal for funding, CV for Tyler Jacobson
    - #47 Kavery Kaul - Long Way From Home, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 76)
      Correspondence, synopsis
    - #49 Maxim Kovalsky - Mere Formality, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - #51 David and Yiuwing Lam - Yah Yah, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      Correspondence, distribution application
    - #52 Tina LaPorta - Total Screen, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      Correspondence, press packet, CV for Tina La Porta, fliers
    - #54 Laura Levine - Digging for Dutch, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      Correspondence, fliers, copies of news clippings
    - #55 David Liacata - Tango Octogenario, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - #57 Paul Lombardi - Delve Volume 1, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - #58 Mary Magasmen and Stephan Hillerbrand - Air Hunger, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      Correspondence, application packet
    - #59 Lina Matta and Odile Isralson - Prison Lullabies, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - #60 Aaron Matthews - A Panther in Africa, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - #62Gabriela Monroy and Louky Keijsers - The Dialogue I and The Dialogue II, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 86)
      Correspondence, texts handed out at screenings, fliers
    - #63 Yasuki Nakajima - After the Apocalypse, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - #64 Julia Newman - Into the Fire: American Women in the Spanish Civil War, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 88)
      Correspondence, press release, fliers program for the Vermont International Film Festival 2002
    - #65 Dana Offenbach - Love and Orgasms, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - #67 Julie Pham - Non-Disclosure, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - #68 Andrea Polli - Atmospherics/Weather Works, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 91)
      Correspondence, fliers
    - #70 Bernie Roddy - Dire Mastery, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - #71 Tom Roe - Radio Single, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - #72 Jeff Root - Free School, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - #73 Barbara Rosenthal - Conceptual Animations, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - #74 Ann T. Rossetti - Pills, Profits, Protest: Voices of Global AIDS Activists, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 96)